as they say great things come in small
packages
this is the n1 pro front dash cam it is
eighty dollars on the website or amazon
but if you use my affiliate code you can
get 20 off on the official bantu website
linked below i received this product for
free to give an honest review of their
product
with the n1 pro i also got the 64
gigabyte vantu sd card which is
recommended to go with the dash cams
that you can get on amazon or the
official website
now i'm going to begin the unboxing
when you open the box the first thing
you'll see are two stickers that you can
put on the window of your car if you
like
underneath that is the quick start guide
and the manual
i'll be going through the pages of the
quick start guide you can either skip
the section or if you do want to read it
you can pause the video so you can take
your time to reading each section
next in the package is the dashcam
itself the n1 pro is smaller than i
expected and it's smaller than the other
bantu products that i own it fits in the
palm of my hand and it feels very
compact and very well built
underneath the dash cam there's the
reset button and the hdmi port if you
want to connect to a bigger screen
on the side is where you would put in
the micro sd card and then the charging
port above it
here on the back you can see that has
four main buttons the power button up
arrow ok button and down arrow
the top button is very important when
you need to save a video and not have it
get overwritten
i'm going to take off the film off the
camera and then let's go into the box
and see what else is inside
inside the accessory box we have three
items
first is the suction cup mount the
suction cup mount has the attachment
that goes directly with the dash cam
on the side is a usb plug that you
connect the power source
the way to lock and unlock the suction
cup mount is by moving the lever from
left to right
next in the accessory box is the usb
wire this you can plug into the dash cam
and then attach it to either a laptop or
computer to upload your footage
the third item in the accessory box is
what goes into your car this is what
charges the dash cam whenever the car is
on you put it in the cigarette slot and
then you plug it into the port of the
suction cup mount
let's dive into setting up the dash cam
the first thing i want to do is install
the micro sd card and format it in the
dash cam i'll be using the micro usb
charging wire to power the dash cam
while i'm setting it up
since the m1 pro is only a front dash
cam i got the 64 gigabyte vantu sd card
because i felt that was a good storage
amount for just the front camera
in my other dash cams i have larger sd
card sizes but
this one i thought 64 gigabytes was
sufficient enough
to get into the menu i pressed ok to
stop recording then i press the power
button to go into the menu and use the
arrows to navigate through the menu you
press ok to enter and you press the
power button to go back
under system settings is where you find
format sd card and once you format the
sd card you can then customize the
settings of your dashcam
for this portion of setting up my dash
cam i set up the video times 2 since
this is mostly based on your preference
you can pause the video if you did want
to see what i put as my settings but
overall it's depending on what you want
i highly recommend choosing the highest
resolution that the dash cam can offer
so you have the best chance of capturing
any detail in the video such as the
license plate
another setting i recommend to customize
is the stamps that go over the video i
do take off a few so then i can see more
of the video than have a bunch of the
stamps covering the video on the top and
bottom i personally take off the logo
stamp the speed stamp and also the
license plate stamp
you finish setting up the dash cam to
exit the menu press the power button to
go back and you start recording again
you will press the ok button you see
that it's recording with the red button
on the left side of the screen and then
the blue button on the dash cam itself
to clarify the controls again the power
button is like the back button while the
ok button is like the enter button and
the arrows is to go left or right and up
and down in the menu the next important
feature of the dashcam is how to save a
video clip so it doesn't get overwritten
if you're in an unfortunate accident the
button is on top of the dashcam it's the
one that's red and you would press it
while it's recording to save the clip
you will see that it's saved with the
key icon on the video
to find the video clip that you just
saved you will go into the menu and go
into files events and you will see the
video clip that has the red key
to play the video you will press ok and
the video will start playing
now that the dash cream is all set up i
want to attach it to the extra cup mount
so that we can start getting some
footage you attach them out until you
hear a click to know that it's connected
to remove it you would press the tab and
then pull the dash cam in the mount
apart
now let's dive in to the dashing footage
itself i got it from the early morning
midday and at night
so
yeah yeah
thank you thank you very much
thankfully the n1 pro in this clip
catches enough of the car that almost
hits me
but
i do wish i had more points of view to
see what happened more clearly that's
why i recommend getting one of the
higher end dash cams from vantrue at
least a two camera or the n43 channel
dashcam that i own
here you can see the car on the left
appears and as we go forward i'm in the
far right lane while it goes into the
left lane which becomes the middle lane
and as you can see it looks like he's
trying to go straight while my car is
here
he pees at me in annoyance but i can't
do much since i'm already in my lane and
as i go into the quick check he also
beats at me again
using a blinker while we're already in
all lanes doesn't give you the right of
way and thankfully with the dash cam if
he had hit me at least there would be
evidence showing that i was in my lane
he was in his lane and he had to yield
but thankfully there was no contact
between our cars and we went away
aside from that event everything else
went smoothly
i do believe the m1 pro is a good
starter dash cam for new people who
don't have a dash cam yet if you're
looking to upgrade though from a dash
cam to another one i do recommend other
products from van true that offer 2k or
4k resolution
front and back cameras as well because
the front camera is a good starter but
you really are missing a lot from not
having a back camera or if you do uber
eats or any of the delivery jobs it is
best recommended to have front and
interior camera besides just the front
i do hope this review has helped you in
your decision in getting the n1 pro
though if you have any questions about
it you can comment below and i'll try my
best to help you with it um i definitely
think it's a great solid camera though
it's so easy to get through the menu and
to just learn how to use it and it has a
lot of features for 80 dash cam
and it's very small so it's not easy to
spot in your car
thank you for watching and i hope you
have a great day stay safe out there and
goodbye